sanramon.org 2011-05-28

# Privacy Statement | San Ramon Chamber of Commerce

We collect personal information about you and all our clients from the information you submit on our applications or other forms, and through information, we obtain over the course of your business relationship with our affiliates, others, and us. In addition, we may from time to time receive information about you from a consumer-reporting agency.

As a rule, we will not disclose any personal information about our clients or former clients to anyone, consistent with our professional confidentiality obligations. However, upon your request, we will disclose information about you, and we may be required by law to disclose personal information about you, as, for example, in response to a subpoena or other court order.

In addition, if requested by you, we may disclose personal information about you to your team of financial and legal advisor firms. In all such situations, we stress the confidential nature of information being shared. We employ precautions to maintain the security of our data transmitted via computer. We use the services of a document shredding company to destroy paper records no longer required. Instructions' regarding client confidentiality has always been a part of our employee manual. We provide access to your personal information only to those employees who need to know the information to provide you with our services. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to guard your personal information. We have been and continue to be bound by professional standards of confidentiality that are even more stringent than those required by law. 

We pledge equal access to services and employment regardless of race, color, religion, gender, age, national origin, disability, or sexual orientation. Please call us if you would like to review this or any other matter in detail.
